{
	"bank" : {	
		"categories" : [		
			{				
				"name" : "Course" ,
				"questions" : [				
					{					
						"question" : "Who is the instructor of our course?",
						"answer" : "Fangju Wang",
						"points" : 10
					} ,	
					{					
						"question" : "How long does our course last for?",
						"answer" : "Twelve Weeks",
						"points" : 20
					} ,	
					{					
						"question" : "On what date is A3 due?",
						"answer" : "December third",
						"points" : 35
					} ,	
					{					
						"question" : "How much is A3 worth?",
						"answer" : "Twenty percent",
						"points" : 60
					} ,																								
				]															
			} ,
			{				
				"name" : "ASR" ,
				"questions" : [				
					{					
						"question" : "What is the main component of the Sphinx4 system?",
						"answer" : "Recognizer",
						"points" : 10
					} ,	
										{					
						"question" : "In Sphinx4, which component is responsible for converting speech signals into feature vectors?",
						"answer" : "FrontEnd",
						"points" : 20
					} ,	
										{					
						"question" : "In Sphinx4, which component is responsible for recognizing the correct speech?",
						"answer" : "Decoder",
						"points" : 35
					} ,	
										{					
						"question" : "In Sphinx4, which component generates the search graph?",
						"answer" : "Linguist",
						"points" : 60
					} ,	
				]											
			} ,	
			{				
				"name" : "Canada" ,
				"questions" : [				
					{					
						"question" : "St. John's is the capital of which province in Canada?",
						"answer" : "Newfoundland",
						"points" : 10
					} ,	
										{					
						"question" : "What is the largest of the North American Great Lakes?",
						"answer" : "Lake Superior",
						"points" : 20
					} ,	
										{					
						"question" : "What is the largest lake that is entirely within Canada?",
						"answer" : "Great Bear Lake",
						"points" : 35
					} ,	
										{					
						"question" : "The Yukon Territory is the only province or territory in Canada that borders on Alaska.",
						"answer" : "False",
						"points" : 60
					} ,	
				]											
			}				
		]
	
	}	
}
